Okay, so before adding the flashlight, what we will do is we will make the environment
dark.
Okay, we will make a night scene in our environment.
You can also skip this video if you like the daytime in the game of white, but I'm going
to change the time to night so that it looks up here to horror and scary, right?
So in order to do that, you need to open up this environment.
On GameObject and then in this environment, if you scroll down a bit, you will find this
sun right here.
And if you turn it off, as you can see, it removes the lightning, the light, okay, or you
can see the sun from the game.
So I'm just going to move this outside, okay, we need to, I think, unpack it, but I'm just
going to disable it for now, okay?
And then after this, when you disable it, you will have to click on this lightning right
here.
If you can't find this lightning window, then you can click on window, then rendering
and in the rendering, you will find this lightning window, right?
And then it will open up right here or anywhere.
So you can go ahead and check it.
So when you have this lightning window, just click on it.
Then let's change right here.
And then what we're going to do is we're going to ink the intensity, multiply it to 0,
so that it is fully dark in the environment.
And then I'm going to change this value to 0.484, alright, and we can leave this as 1, and
then we can run on the fog as well, as you can see, the fog are the white thing, as
we can see in the environment.
So you can run on the fog, and for the fog, we need to change the fog color.
So the color of the fog will be this value, okay?
You can go ahead and type this hexadecimal value, which is 2, 0, 3, 1, 4, okay?
And there is this blue kind of color, alright?
And let me tell you that you can choose your own lightning, okay?
I prefer to plug in this zombie game.
So if you want, you can just follow me step by step, alright?
So once you do all this, then what we're going to do is let's click on Inspector and
right in the Inspector, what we're going to do now is add directional light, alright?
So if you click on this light right here in the narrow directional light, now as you can
see, it is again daytime in this game, alright?
So I'm just going to leave this as directional light, then we need to change the color
of this light, which will be the same color as we did before, which is 2, 0, 3, 1, 4e, alright?
And the intensity of this will be 0.1, alright?
And then the shadows will be soft shadows, because of course this is a PC game, we want
shadows in it, okay?
And I think that will be it for this directional light.
After this directional light, we can also add some post processing as well, okay?
So what I'm going to do is, I'm going to create a empty camera check, name it as Post
Process, and then to this, I'm going to add the post process volume, okay?
And in the profile, we can select this PC desktop.
And then if you turn it off and on, as you can see, there are some few changes right
now, what I'm going to do is I'm going to change some values, okay?
So we have all of these options, let's turn them on and now let's change values.
So the ambient collision will be the same, the motion blur as well, then we have bloom.
So if you want to increase the bloom, you can do it, alright?
But I'm going to just leave it as it is, then we have this color grading and in the color
grilling, you can turn on the low definition range and then we have this right here, okay?
It is on, but as you can see, it doesn't affect the environment.
That is because if you open up the camera, on the camera, as you can see, the post process
fluid clones is added, alright?
If we add it again, alright, I'll write it again, let me check.
I think we already have a post process, so that means, yes, to leave this, I think we had
that, but we disable it and I forgot to enable it again, okay?
So in the environment to be deleted, we have this post process volume as I told you in
the start, that make sure that you don't delete these, okay?
You can run that on again, as you can see, all of the things are already added right here,
okay?
And now you can increase and decrease these values, so what I'm going to do, I'm going
to just change the last, I don't know how to pronounce this week, week netty or whatever
it is called, you can just change it's well, okay?
So I want a little bit darkness on the edges like that, okay?
So I'm just going to leave this intensity as 0.45, alright, and then you can just try and
drop this in the player related, okay?
And also the directional light, the P2226, and that is it, alright, now if we go ahead
and play the game, alright, here we are, now as you can see, it is coming.
Complete dark, okay?
And I think we need to change the values a little bit if we click on directional light, alright,
and yes, here we are, just make sure that you change the directional light value, because
right now it is really dark, and if you notice this guy is blue, so of course we want
the environment to be shown a little bit, okay, so I think 1 point, let me try it to,
okay, I think 2 will be a good value for it, okay?
So you can stop the game and change the intensity to 2, alright, and then let's go ahead
and play the game again, and now as you can see it looks really good now, alright, everything
is showing and now it looks really good, but now if you notice we can't see in some of the
areas, because it is really dark in there, so that's why for that reason we will be adding
the flashlight to the player and also as you know that, here somewhere there is a gun,
and of course the player will not know where the gun is, okay, so we like nails, the
pick up items or an objective which the player have to do, we will add some kind of
a lamp here, so that the player know that there is something to be interacted with, okay,
So now, with this done, let's end this video right here.